Guide to the Junior League of Brooklyn records ARC.304
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 3: Accounting and Financial, 1941-2000; 21731
  - Administrative receipts ledger (April 1941-April 1944), 1941-1944; 21749 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Administrative receipts ledger (Oct. 1944-May 1948), 1944-1948; 21750 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Administrative receipts ledger (Aug. 1948-Jan. 1953), 1948-1953; 21751 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Administrative receipts ledger (July 1961-May 1965), 1961-1965; 21752 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Administrative receipts ledger, 1984; 21753 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Administrative disbursements ledger (Apr. 1941-Jan. 1946), 1941-1946; 21754 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Administrative disbursements ledger (Sept. 1960-May 1965), 1960-1965; 21755 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - General ledger, 1965-1966; 21756 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - General ledger, 1966-1967; 21757 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - General ledger (pages), 1968-1973; 21758 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - General ledger (pages), 1979-1980; 21759 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - General ledger (pages), 1980-1981; 21760 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - General ledger (pages), 1981-1982; 21761 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - General ledger (pages), 1982-1984; 21762 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Gala preview party ledger, 1987; 21763 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Community trust fund ledger, 1952-1965; 21764 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Series 4: Committees and Task Forces, 1939-2000; 21732
  The series is composed of records of member committees and external advisors. These records include correspondence and meeting minutes of the Community Advisory Council, documents pertaining to the membership diversification efforts and task force implementation, membership admissions and training, project studies, and agencies. A large portion of records in this series also relate to the planning and execution of volunteer placement for the membership. Related materials can be found in Series 2: Meetings and Minutes (based on date), and Series 5: Subject Files (based on agency, event or activity). Materials related to the Council Implementation committee can be found in Series 1: Administrative Records, "Council system - 1987,1998." Items in this series are in fair to excellent condition.
  - Central volunteer placement bureau, circa 1900s; 21765 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Child advocacy committee, 1974-1983; 21766 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Children's task force, 1977-1991; 21767 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Community advisory council, 1978-1984; 21768 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Community advisory council, 1986-1994; 21769 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Community advisory council, 1998-1999; 21770 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Community advisory council: Minutes, 1978-1994; 21771 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Community advisory council: Member lists, 1986-1994; 21772 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Computer committee, 1982-1986; 21773 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Council implementation committee, 1999-2000; 21774 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Cultural task force, 1979-1992; 21775 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Elected officials forum committee, 1991-1992; 21776 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Finance committee, 1982-1988; 21777 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Finance committee, 1998-1999; 21778 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Fund development committee, 1991; 21779 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Future planning committee, 1980-1991; 21780 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Membership and admissions committee, 1916-1926; 21781 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Membership and admissions committee, 1927-1954; 21782 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Membership and admissions committee (pages), 1939-1959; 21783 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Membership committee, 1998-1999; 21784 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Membership development committee, 1983-1998; 21785 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Membership diversity team, 1989-1998; 21786 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Newssheet committee, 1979-1995; 21787 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Operations committee, 1978-1984; 21788 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Parks and recreation task force, 1980-1982; 21789 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Nominating/placement committee, 1979-1993; 21790 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Nominating/placement committee, 1997-1998; 21791 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Placement committee: Agencies, 1961-1970; 21792 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Placement books, 1979-1984; 21793 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Placement books, 1984-1999; 21794 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Placement pool and fair, 1984-1988; 21795 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Placement fair, 1994-1995, 2000; 21796 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - President's ad-hoc search committee, 1983; 21797 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Project study committee: Correspondence, 1951-1956; 21798 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Project study committee: Minutes and notes, 1962-1968; 21799 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Project study committee: Planning materials, 1954-1957; 21800 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Project study committee: Reports, 1950-1956; 21801 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Project meetings, 1986, 1988; 21802 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Public affairs committee, 1983-1997; 21803 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Public affairs committee, 1998-1999; 21804 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Public affairs training, 1985-1986, 1994; 21805 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Public relations committee, 1947-1984; 21806 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Special task force on equity and excellence in education, 1980; 21807 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Strategic planning committee, 1998-1999; 21808 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Task force meetings, 1984-1986; 21809 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Task forces planning, 1976-1998; 21810 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Task forces books, 1976-1978; 21811 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Task forces books, 1978-1979; 21812 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Teen/AIDS committee, 1990; 21813 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Training committee, 1976-1979; 21814 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Training committee, 1993-1999; 21815 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Training committee: Questionnaires, 1981-1982; 21816 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Training and placement planning materials, 1976-1979; 21817 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Training and placement planning materials, 1980-1982; 21818 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Training and placement planning materials, 1983; 21819 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Training and placement planning materials, 1984; 21820 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Training and placement planning materials, 1987-1998; 21821 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Urban task force, 1980-1992; 21822 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- Series 5: Subject Files, 1927-2002; 21733
  The series holds records of anniversaries and other events, League projects and associated agencies, fundraising, public relations, research and other activities. The series is arranged alphabetically. Related materials are found in Series 4: Committees and Task Forces. Public relations materials contain some press photographs of League leadership and special events.
  - 70th Anniversary, 1980; 21823 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - 75th Anniversary Kick-off: Diamond Jubilee Party, 1985; 21824 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - 80th Anniversary Misteltoe Champagne Gala, 1990; 21825 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - 81st Anniversary Holiday Gala, 1991; 21826 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - 85th Anniversary Ball, 1995; 21827 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - American Cancer Society, 1983-1984; 21828 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Arts and crafts: Dolls and animals, circa 1950-1960; 21829 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Arts and crafts: General, 1954; 21830 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Arts and crafts: Workbooks, circa 1950-1960, 1959; 21831 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Atlantic Terminal, 1967-1968; 21832 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - "Babes in Brooklyn", 1972; 21833 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Brooklyn Association of Teen Educators (BATES), 1992-1993; 21834 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Brooklyn Bureau of Community Service, 1998; 21835 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Brooklyn Bureau of Social Service, 1961-1963, 1968; 21836 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Brooklyn Child Advocacy Center, 1997; 21837 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Brooklyn Child Advocacy Center, 1998-1999; 21838 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Brooklyn Children's Museum (MUSE), 1970; 21839 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Brooklyn Children's Museum (MUSE), 1984-1985; 21840 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - The Brooklyn Club, 1987; 21841 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Brooklyn Heights Association, 1981-1984; 21842 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Brooklyn Heights house tour, 1972; 21843 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Brooklyn Historic Railway Association, 1982-1984; 21844 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Brooklyn In-Touch Information Center, 1982-1985; 21845 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Brooklyn Kindergarten Society, circa 1900s; 21846 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Brooklyn Museum, 1983-1985; 21847 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Brooklyn Museum and the Metropolitan Museum of Art: Slideshow Projects, 1971, 1975; 21848 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Brooklyn Public Library, 1997-1998; 21849 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Brooklyn Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Children, 1962; 21850 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - "A Brooklyn Tradition" - cookbook, 1992; 21851 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - "Brooklyn Works" business to business expo, 1984-1985; 21852 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Brookwood Child Care, 1985-1986, 1992; 21853 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Calico Ball, 1930; 21854 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - The CAP Book, Inc., 1979, 1985; 21855 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - "Celebrating 80 Years of Service", 1990; 21856 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Chicken dinners, 1985; 21857 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Child abuse and neglect, 1974-1978; 21858 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Children's History Room, 1964-1965; 21859 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Children in Placement (C.I.P.) Project, 1978-1980; 21860 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Children in Placement (C.I.P.) Project, 1981; 21861 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Children's theatre, 1938-1956; 21862 (Box 44, Folder -)
  - Children's theatre committee, 1963-1965; 21863 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Children's theatre: Marionette/puppetry, 1952-1956; 21864 (Box 44, Folder -)
  - Children's theatre: Planning materials, 1953-1957; 21865 (Box 44, Folder -)
  - Children's theatre: Correspondence, 1957; 21866 (Box 44, Folder -)
  - Citizens' Committee for Children of New York, 1971-1975; 21867 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Coalition of Organizations and Advocates for Children, 1979-1980; 21868 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Community board, 1984; 21869 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Congressional districts, circa 1900s; 21870 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Corrective reading clinic project, 1963-1967; 21871 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Crown Heights Youth Collective, 1993-1995; 21872 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Dances, 1923-1955, 1969; 21873 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Day care center: Correspondence, 1968-1975; 21874 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Day care center: Planning materials, 1969-1975; 21875 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Day care center: Research, 1973, 1981, 1983; 21876 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Decorator's Show House, 1987-1988; 21877 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Decorator's Show House: Slides, 1987; 21878 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Effective Community Involvement, 1977; 21882 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Esteem team, 1998-1999; 21883 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Events, 1927-1991; 21881 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Facilitator training, 1983; 21884 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Family well-being, 1982-1983; 21885 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Fashion shows, 1933, circa 1950-1960; 21886 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Fulton Ferry project, 1984; 21887 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Fundraising, 1976-1993; 21888 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Fundraising, 1994-1997; 21889 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Fundraising, 1998; 21890 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Fundraising, 1999; 21891 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Golden Anniversary Ball, 1960; 21892 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Golden Anniversary Ball: Programs, 1960; 21893 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Governor's Conference on Families, 1979-1980; 21894 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Graham-Windham Services, 1991-1994; 21895 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Hearing centers for children: Research, 1953-1954; 21896 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Heights and Hill Community Council, 1976-1984; 21897 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Heights-Hill Mental Health Service, 1993; 21898 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Hemisphere Ball, 1962; 21899 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - History of the JLB slideshow project, 1990; 21900 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - History of the JLB slideshow project: Slides, 1990; 21901 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Holiday dinner, 1986; 21902 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - HOPE Program, 1992-1993; 21908 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Immunization awareness project, 1990-1991; 21909 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Job resource directory, 1995; 21910 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Junior League Disaster Relief Fund, 2002; 21911 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Junior Leagues outside of Brooklyn, 1962-1998; 21912 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Juvenile justice, 1975; 21913 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Latchkey children, 1985; 21914 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - The League Center, 1983-1984; 21915 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Lectures, 1930-1939; 21916 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Legal advisory, 1983-1984; 21917 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Literacy volunteering, 1976-1984; 21918 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Long Island College Hospital, 1985-1986; 21919 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous, 1991-1993; 21920 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Montague School, 1975-1976; 21921 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Neighborhood Family Services Coalition, 1982-1983; 21922 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Neighborhood Family Services Coalition, 1984-1985; 21923 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - New York City Commision on the Status of Women, 1985-1986; 21924 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - New York City Guidebook for the Handicapped, 1969-1971; 21925 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - New York City Parks and Recreation, 1991; 21926 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - New York City Self-Help Clearinghouse, 1983-1984; 21927 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - New York City Self Help Clearinghouse: Office, 1989-1992; 21928 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - New York City Youth Board, 1963-1971; 21929 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Operation Breakfast, 1970-1972; 21930 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Parenting Education Program of Brooklyn, 1976-1985; 21931 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Peer tutoring guide, 1983; 21932 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Pierrepont Street Playground, 1973-1974; 21933 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Plays for the Living, circa 1980; 21934 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Premature Center Program, 1959-1968; 21935 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Presidential Recognition Award, 1983; 21936 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Private school scholarship program: research, 1969; 21937 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Project LEAD, 1983-1986; 21938 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Project Proposals, 1957-1970, 1983, 1992; 21939 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Prospect Park Guide, 1980-1992; 21940 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Provisional membership, 1925; 21941 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Provisional membership, 1977-1979; 21942 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Provisional membership, 1980-1984; 21943 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Provisional membership, 1987-1996; 21944 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Provisional membership courses, 1979-1982; 21945 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Public lectures, 1979; 21946 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Public policy issues, 1980-2002; 21947 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Public relations, 1976-1991; 21948 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Public relations, 1992-1997; 21949 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Public relations: Scrapbook, 1987-1989; 21950 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Public relations: Scrapbook, 1989-1991; 21951 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Radio Prime Time, 1983-1985; 21952 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Radio Prime Time: Audio cassette tapes, 1985; 21953 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Rape crisis intervention program/video, 1988-1993; 21954 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Rape crisis intervention program/video, 1993-1998; 21955 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Salute to Youth, Inc., 1970; 21956 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Sanitary Fair and Ball, 1930; 21957 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Scholarship fundraising breakfast, 1985; 21958 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Scholarship fundraising breakfast: Programs, 1985; 21959 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Seminars: general, 1967-2002; 21960 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Silent Witness Initiative, 1996; 21961 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Silent Witness Initiative: Press book, 1996; 21962 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Silent Witness Inintiative: Presentation transparacies, 1967-2002; 21963 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Silent Witness Initiative: Templates, 1967-2002; 21964 (Box 40, Folder -)
  - Social Work Fellowship, 1960-1970; 21965 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Social Work Fellowship: Applications, 1961-1965; 21966 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - The Support Center, 1981-1983; 21967 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Sustainers, 1968-1999; 21968 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Sustainers Questionnaire, 1983; 21969 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Talbot Perkins Adoption Services, 1961; 21970 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Task management, 1992-1995; 21971 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Theatre productions: "Gammer Gurton's Needle", 1942; 21972 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Theatre productions: "Gay Nineties", 1939; 21973 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Theatre productions: "Hansel and Gretel", 1941; 21974 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Theatre productions: "Hansel and Gretel" score, circa 1940; 21975 (Box 44, Folder -)
  - Theatre productions: "Jack and the Beanstalk", 1943-1944; 21976 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Theatre productions: "The Little Green Flower", 1943; 21977 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Theatre productions: "The Man of La Mancha", 1985; 21978 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Theatre productions: Photographs, 1967-2002; 21979 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Theatre productions: Planning materials and programs, 1967-2002, 1927-1934, 1950; 21980 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Theatre productions: "Snow Follies", 1940; 21981 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Underground Society Bash, 1977; 21982 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Venetian Masked Ball, 1985; 21983 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Venetian Masked Ball: Past Presidents' Dinner, 1985; 21984 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Volunteer of the Year, 1979-1987; 21985 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Website, 1998; 21986 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - "Welcome Back to Brooklyn", 1987-1988, 1992; 21987 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - White House Conference on Families, 1979; 21988 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - WNYE-TV, 1966-1967; 21989 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Women's History Month, 1993-1994; 21990 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - "Woman to Woman" alcohol awareness project, 1986-1988; 21991 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Women's Survival Space, 1988-1997; 21992 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - World's Fair Ball, 1964; 21993 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - YWCA of Brooklyn, 1990-1995; 21994 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Youth violence prevention resolution, 1994; 21995 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Series 6: Court Appointed Special Advocates (CASA), 1974-1991; 21734
  The series consists of records pertaining to the JLB's involvement in the Court Appointed Special Advocates (CASA) program which provided trained advocates for abused, neglected or abandoned children in the foster care and court system. Materials also pertain to the Children in Placement Project (CIP), the precursor to CASA, a program developed in the Family Court of New York City to monitor placements of children in foster care. Items include project proposals, case notes, correspondence, fundraising and other financial documents, reports and research materials, and publications. Some items in this series contain sensitive information regarding individual cases and confidential information about employees of the program. These records must be handled with discretion.
  - Court Appointed Special Advocates (CASA), 1979-1991; 21996 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - CASA - advisory board, 1990-1991; 21997 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - CASA - advisory board meeting minutes, 1979-1981; 21998 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - CASA - cases, 1979-1980; 21999 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - CASA - Children in Placement (CIP) Program: general, 1979-1980; 22000 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - CASA - CIP: project proposals, 1980; 22001 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - CASA - CIP: notes by Neita Blondeau, 1978-1979; 22002 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - CASA - correspondence, 1978-1980; 22003 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - CASA - correspondence, 1981; 22004 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - CASA - correspondence, 1982-1983; 22005 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - CASA - employee information, 1982-1984; 22006 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - CASA - fundraising, 1978-1983; 22007 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - CASA - incorporation of CASA, 1981-1984; 22008 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - CASA - insurance, 1982-1983; 22009 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - CASA: "A Long Way from Home: Infants in Search of Adoptive Families", 1983; 22010 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - CASA - notice of appeal to deny CASA access to child's case, 1980; 22011 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - CASA - "The Parents' Handbook: A Guide for Parents of Children in Foster Care", 1976; 22012 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - CASA - planning materials, 1980-1981; 22013 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - CASA - project proposals, 1979-1981; 22014 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - CASA - public relations, 1980-1991; 22015 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - CASA - reports, 1979-1981; 22016 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - CASA - research materials, 1977-1978; 22017 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - CASA - resources in New York, 1974, 1980; 22018 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - CASA - services contract, circa 1979; 22019 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - CASA - training materials, 1978-1981; 22020 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - CASA - transcript of speech by Penny Ferrer, 1980; 22021 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - CASA - accounts ledger (pages), 1980-1984; 22022 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - CASA - check stubs, 1982-1984; 22023 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - CASA - check stubs from Citibank account, 1979-1981; 22024 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - CASA - checks paid from Citibank account, 1979-1981; 22025 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - CASA - checks paid from Citibank account, 1982; 22026 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - CASA - checks paid from Citibank account, 1983-1984; 22027 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - CASA - checks paid and statements from Chase bank, 1983-1984; 22028 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - CASA - finances, 1979-1981; 22029 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - CASA - finances, 1982-1985; 22030 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - CASA - payroll book, 1983; 22031 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Series 7: Association of Junior Leagues International, Inc. (AJLI), 1959-2002; 22032
  The series is comprised of documents pertaining to the relationship of the Junior League of Brooklyn and the Association of Junior Leagues International, Inc. (AJLI). AJLI was formed in 1921 and provides continuity, support, guidance, and leadership development opportunities to 293 Junior Leagues in the United States, Canada, Mexico, and the United Kingdom. Items include conference materials, annual questionnaires, board minutes and reports, administrative documents, correspondence, mailings, input packets, programs and workshops, strategic planning and public relations materials.
  - Association of Junior Leagues (AJLI) - administration, 1981-2002; 22033 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - AJLI - administration handbook, 1981; 22034 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - AJLI - annual conference, 1984; 22035 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - AJLI - annual conference, 1985; 22036 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - AJLI - annual conference, 1986; 22037 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - AJLI - annual conference, 1987; 22038 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - AJLI - annual conference, 1988; 22039 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - AJLI - annual conference, 1992-1999; 22040 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - AJLI - annual digests, 1972-1973, 1975; 22041 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - AJLI - annual questionnaires, 1959-1965; 22042 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - AJLI - annual questionnaires, 1966-1969; 22043 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - AJLI - annual questionnaires, 1972-1975; 22044 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - AJLI - annual questionnaires, 1976-1980; 22045 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - AJLI - annual questionnaires, 1980-1984; 22046 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - AJLI - annual questionnaires, 1985-1989; 22047 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - AJLI - annual questionnaires, 1989-1990; 22048 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - AJLI - annual reports, 1973-1979; 22049 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - AJLI - annual reports, 1980-1991; 22050 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - AJLI - Area I, 1972-1979; 22051 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - AJLI - Area I, 1982, 1984-1993; 22052 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - AJLI - Area I, 1983; 22053 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - AJLI - Area I Council positions, 1985; 22054 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - AJLI - Association By-laws, 1985-1986, 1959-2002; 22055 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - AJLI - "Automation Guidelines for Junior Leagues", 1982-1985; 22056 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - AJLI - Awards, 1994-1998; 22057 (Box 24, Folder 4)